Hi.
I'm Leanne Mclntyre.
I'm an attorney.
My client asked
me to give you this.
He caught someone trying to plant
it in his house yesterday afternoon.
He's fairly certain it's the same
gun used to kill Dennis Spiers.
And the intruder, whom
he didn't recognize,
is trying to frame
him for that murder.
Have a nice day. Bye-bye.
Hold it. Hold it.
Your client got a name?
Well, of course. Bye.
It wouldn't be Ed Wingate,
by any chance, would it?
- Oh, is Ed Wingate a suspect?
- We searched his house
and found Dennis Spiers'
watch and gold cufflinks.
So you tell Ed Wingate
the sooner he gets his butt in here
to answer some questions, the better.
If I see him, I'm gonna
tell him. Bye-bye.
You're making me very nervous.
I'm not making a pass at you,
Bink. I just want a little information.
I shouldn't be talking to you.
I'm not a murderer, Bink.
Keep eating.
Make it look like you're
chewing when you talk.
Did you tell anyone about
the fight Spiers and I had?
Alan Pierce, Brenda Farrell,
some police lieutenant.
They were asking me a whole
bunch of questions about Dennis
the morning after he was killed.
Well, I'm sorry.
It just slipped out.
That's okay.
Why were they asking you
questions about Dennis?
They knew he called
me the night before.
About what?
He was pretty sure
he had found the house
where the Sanborn
kid was being held.
Wanted me to analyze some motor
oil he'd found in the driveway there.
Motor oil?
Where is this house?
He didn't say.
- Do you still have the oil?
- Yeah.
I'm going to send you
another sample this afternoon.
I want you to compare the two, see
if they came from the same engine.
Ugh. If they find
out what I'm doing...
They won't.
I'll be in touch.
Hey.
Your slip is showing.
Thank you.
I can't tell you
how worried I was.
I felt helpless.
Pop, it was the worst
four days of my life.
Worse than the time Brewster
Sherwood took your bike apart
and hung the pieces
down in the outhouse?
- Oh, much worse, ten times worse.
- Ha, ha.
Although that was pretty bad.
- Yeah. Pass the ketchup.
- Uh...
Anything else you want?
Do you want another hot dog?
I already had two. What
are you trying to do to me?
You look a little thin. I'm
just trying to fatten you up.
There is one thing
you can do for me.
Anything. You just name
it. Anything you want.
Be Barry and Tracey's lawyer.
You want me to defend the
people who kidnapped you?
They're broke.
Unless you do it, they're liable
to get some public defender
who doesn't know diddly
and doesn't give two hoots.
You care what happens to
people who kidnapped you?
They're nice kids.
Stockholm Syndrome.
The what?
People who're held hostage often
wind up sympathizing with their captors,
sometimes to the point
of defecting to their cause.
I've read about it.
I've seen it on TV.
I never thought it'd
happen to my father.
Who's defecting?
I just think they deserve
a fair shake, that's all.
Billy.
Where you been? I been
looking all over for you.
How come you won't
answer my calls?
You know this person?
Pop, it's Ben.
I knew a man named Ben once.
- Thought he was my friend.
- Pop.
Then one day I
saw his true colors.
My life was at stake,
and what did he do?
He bickered over
what it was worth.
I wasn't bickering.
I was stalling.
Tell Mr. "Let's Make A Deal" that as
far as I'm concerned he no longer exists.
Yeah?
Well, you tell Mr. "Let's Be
Ungrateful As Hell" that he's a jerk.
How'd you get in here?
Quietly. I didn't
mean to scare you.
Ugh.
I wonder if you'd
do me a small favor.
Oh.
Would you deliver this
oil sample to the FBI lab,
see that it gets to a
techie named Bink.
Thanks.
- Can I ask you something?
- Anything.
Well, one day you come
in here in a Hawaiian shirt.
The next day you come in
dressed like a construction worker.
Sometimes I wear a dress.
I wouldn't be surprised.
You wear those
dark glasses at night.
You're the wind.
I really don't get that one.
How'd you get so far up in the FBI?
Results.
I work hard, go the extra
mile, get the job done.
I'm really not very
different than you.
- We're alike?
- Yeah.
Ha, ha, I don't think so.
- Do you dress like other lawyers?
- Um, I don't know.
- Do you live in a big house?
- No.
You figure, if you get
your client off, that's the job.
Doesn't matter how you
look, or where you live.
You won't even tell people
what law school you went to.
You're all right,
Ed. You're all right.
I wouldn't want you to marry
my daughter, but you're all right.
Oh, that's okay.
We're probably not
very compatible, anyway.
- Huh?
- She takes herself too seriously.
Yes?
Well, Mr. Bingham, what brings
you up from the bowels of the lab?
Well, something kind
of bizarre is going on,
and I figured I'd better talk to
somebody before it got any bizarrer.
Sit down.
You know how Ed
Wingate always claims
that some person planted
the gun in his house,
the one that killed
Dennis Spiers,
so it would look like he
was the one who offed him?
Yes.
- Well, I kind of ran into him today.
- You saw Ed Wingate?
- Yes. Where?
- Well, actually...
In a restaurant downtown, he
was doing one of his drag numbers.
Anyway, he asked
me to analyze some oil
that leaked from the car of the guy
that he says planted the gun in his house.
I did. And here's
what's really weird.
Not only talked to him,
you did him a favor?
The man is wanted
for questioning.
The oil that Ed
Wingate sent over
matched the sample that Dennis
Spears sent over the night he died.
Are you sure?
Both samples came
from the same engine.
I'm positive.
Brenda? Oh, good, you're
still here. Come to my office.
We may have a break
in the Sanborn case.
Did you tell Ed Wingate?
No. He, uh... He said he'd call.
Good.
Yo, Bink here.
WINGATE: It's Wingate.
Have you compared
the oil samples yet?
Yep. I sure did.
And?
I can't hear you very well, uh, with
all that music there. Where are you?
Never mind. Did they match?
Well, uh, the oils
matched, yeah.
But, uh, did they come from the
same engine? That's the tough part.
Well, did they?
Well, you see,
first I filtered out all of
the particles and, uh...
Did they or didn't they, Bink?
Yes.
How can you be sure?
Well, that's what I
been trying to tell you.
I mean, first I filtered all the
particles out from the sample.
That wasn't easy, you know.
Oh, of course not.
- Then what did you do?
- Oh...
Well, uh...
Hi.
You're with the FBI.
Alan Pierce, special
agent in charge.
This is Agent Farrell.
Well, Agent
Wingate is long gone.
He figured that you
traced the call, heh.
- I'm Ben Matlock.
- No kidding?
Yeah.
Sit down. Have some pizza.
Might as well. Ed
bought it, ha, ha.
Vegetarian,
wouldn't you know it?
Where is he?
Oh, I don't know, and if I did,
I'd be honor bound not to tell you.
Want my pineapple?
I understand he
has some information
that might help us solve
the Sanborn kidnapping case.
Well, all Ed knows
is that whoever
kidnapped Matthew
is the same man that
he saw at his house
planting the jewelry and the gun
that was used to kill Dennis Spiers.
At least, the guy was
driving the same car.
Well, Ed has got to come in
and tell us what he looked like.
Well, he'd love to.
But he's a little concerned
about something. What is that?
Artichoke. MATLOCK: Ew.
- You want it?
- Mr. Matlock.
Uh, well, ahem,
the way Ed sees it,
uh, the kidnapper somehow found
out that Dennis Spiers was onto him.
So, he killed him, and then he
framed Ed to cover for himself.
Uh, the problem is how did
Mr. Kidnapper know to frame Ed?
I mean, he didn't know who
he was, or where he lived,
or the fact that he had just had
a big fight with Dennis Spiers.
- Unless, uh...
- Unless what?
Somebody at the FBI told him.
You suggesting that someone with
the FBI is in business with a kidnapper?
Saints preserve us,
that's how it looks.
You really believe that?
Oh, saints preserve us.
Then you are an idiot.
Just relax. Relax. It's just me.
Sorry I had to sneak in, but
they may be watching the house.
Why are you dressed that way?
Never mind. I
don't want to know.
No, no, no, Ben. Ben.
We have to talk.
Call me in the morning.
They may have tapped the
phone. Oh, come on. Ben.
You weren't sleeping
that well, anyway.
Oh, it was the pizza.
Whoever heard of
putting raisins on a pizza.
There were no
raisins on that pizza.
Listen, uh, I followed Alan
Pierce and Brenda Farrell
after they left the
pizzeria last night.
You did?
I figured they'd be pretty
shaken up after they talked to you.
Oh, uh, they might
have arrested you.
Not me.
Oh, that's right.
You're the wind.
Where'd they go?
Alan Pierce took Brenda Farrell
back to the office to get her car,
where they split up.
Instinct told me to
follow her, which I did,
all the way to South Carolina,
where she has a very nice
beach house right on the water,
with a very nice Porsche
tucked in the garage.
I'll bet she spends
her weekends there.
Hmm, mm-hm.
Is she married?
- Divorced.
- Oh.
- Alimony?
- Zip.
Oh.
Ben,
I have a plan.
Let's talk about
it in the morning.
Ben.
It is morning.
Miss Harrington.
Please.
So, Mr. Lewis, how are you?
I'm fine.
First off,
I want to assure you that
we have a very strong case
against Mr. Feldman
and Miss Riggins,
and I intend to prosecute
them to the full extent of the law.
- I kind of wish you wouldn't.
- I beg your pardon?
I'd like to see them get off.
Stockholm Syndrome.
Well, is he getting help?
Oh, no, no, he doesn't
think he needs it.
You know, you're talking
about me and I'm right here.
Mr. Lewis, kidnapping is
an extremely serious crime.
You're very fortunate.
All too many kidnap
victims wind up dead.
They never wanted to hurt me.
Look at me, there's
not a scratch on me.
All they wanted to do
was get back at Ben.
Who can blame them?
Sending Barry's
brother to prison like that.
Get him help, preferably
before he testifies.
- I'm not gonna testify.
- What?
I refuse to participate
in this tapestry of justice.
- Travesty of justice, Pop.
- You agree, huh?
Look, Mr. Lewis, if I
don't put you on the stand
the jury's gonna think
that something's wrong.
Something is wrong. These
kids shouldn't be on trial.
You are going to testify,
even if I have to subpoena you.
Look, I believe
we're through here.
I'll see you in court.
No, you won't.
Yes, she will.
And it's not gonna be pretty.
What do you mean,
you marked the bills?
The night before, after I'd
gotten the money together,
while we were all waiting
for the kidnapper to call,
I took a blue pen,
and I made little marks next to
Grant on nearly all the 50s like that one.
Huh.
Dr. Sanborn, heh, do you have
any idea how big a chance you took?
- If the kidnapper had discovered it...
- I know.
I know. Heh, I
can't believe I did it.
And Matthew could
have been killed.
I realize that.
I must have been out of my mind.
Why didn't you say something
when Matthew was released?
Why did you wait till now?
Well, to tell you
the truth, I forgot.
I mean, the money seemed
so hideously unimportant
compared to seeing and
holding Matthew again.
As you know, we've been out of
town, and I just forgot. I'm sorry.
Well, I'll get the word out
and see if any of these 50s
have shown up anywhere.
Depending on his spending habits,
it could lead us to the kidnapper.
You lucked out
once, Dr. Sanborn.
Maybe you will again.
My name is Billy Lewis, and I
live in Willow Springs, Georgia.
Your honor, due to the
reluctance of the witness
to voluntarily cooperate
in providing testimony,
the state asks that he be
treated as a hostile witness.
Proceed.
On February 10th of this year,
you were kidnapped. Is that right?
No.
You were escorted at gunpoint
from the home of Ben Matlock.
Were you not?
Yeah, but I wouldn't
call that being kidnapped.
It was more like, uh, getting an
invitation to a come-as-you-are party
that I didn't feel
like refusing.
Do you recognize those
two people over there?
Yeah. That's Barry
Feldman and Tracey Riggins.
I wanted my son
to be their lawyer,
but he gave me a lot of
gas about conflict of interest.
Are those the two people
who escorted you from Mr. Matlock's
home at gunpoint that day?
Well, I, uh, I went with them.
I'm not sure about
that gunpoint stuff.
They made you
lie down in their van
and then tied your hands together
with duct tape, did they not?
Yeah. But they
didn't tie me very tight.
I could have gotten
away if I'd really wanted to.
They took you to a room and
held you prisoner there for four days.
- Correct?
- No.
They housed me.
They fed me donuts
and played cards with me.
But to tell you the truth, it was really
more like, uh, being on a vacation.
Except you weren't
allowed to leave, were you?
Who said I wanted to?
Mr. Feldman made
several calls to Ben Matlock,
saying that he would kill you
if Mr. Matlock didn't pay him a
large sum of money. Did he not?
Now, that's very interesting
that you should mention money and
Ben Matlock in the same sentence,
- because as far as I'm concerned...
- Just answer the question.
She's got a lot of
nerve calling me hostile.
How long do I have to
put up with this, judge?
I couldn't believe it when he
told me he marked the bills.
We never discussed
doing something like that.
He never even
brought up the subject.
Well, no harm done. The
money's still in the safe.
We'll just have to go out
there, pull all the marked bills.
You can launder them next month.
What's next month?
We have to go to
Europe next month.
- Oh, didn't I tell you?
- Heh.
What for?
- Ooh, I will make up something.
- Hmm.
- Oh, did you get ahold of Becker?
- He's going to meet us there.
- Well, come on, let's go.
- Hang on. Hang on.
Do you see that drunk propped up
against the building across the street?
What about him?
He's wearing $200 boots.
You two take care of the money.
I'm gonna take care of
that bozo once and for all.
Hello, Ed.
These people
wanted to talk with you.
So I got on my car phone and
arranged for a little meeting.
Enjoy.
All right. Come on.
Becker.
- How long have you been here?
- A couple of minutes.
Dr. Sanborn marked
the bills, huh?
Just the 50s. Didn't tell
us about it until today.
Where's Farrell?
Handing Wingate
over to the cops.
Okay.
Pull all the bills that
have a blue ink mark
somewhere in the
vicinity of Grant's face.
I don't see any
ink marks. Do you?
All right. Hands
up. Nobody move.
Check the body.
- He's not breathing.
- Check the pulse.
I had to shoot him.
He went for his gun.
That's him. That's the
guy who kidnapped me.
- Who was he?
- Kurt Becker.
Did five years in Walla Walla for
extortion. Released two years ago.
Looks like he picked
up right where he left off.
Thanks, son. You can go now.
- Thank you, lieutenant.
- Very much appreciated.
Thank you so much.
I just want to thank you again
for going to the FBI and
saying you'd marked those bills.
You know, I'm afraid
I still don't understand
- what that was all about.
- Unfortunately, it's a long story
that didn't quite have the
ending we were hoping for.
The kidnapper's dead.
How could you hope for
a better ending than that?
Well, he died before
we could find out
whether he was working
alone or with somebody.
Got your money back.
At least that's something.
We got Matthew back.
That was all that was
really important. Thanks.
Bye.
- Leanne, did you talk to Wingate yet?
- I'm going there now.
- Good. See you in a minute.
- Where are you going?
Hang on.
Hurry up.
Well, heh, you're just
the person I want to see.
- Not now. Not now.
- Where the hell do you get off
interfering with an FBI
investigation like that?
I've gotta get in there. My daughter
made me drink fruit juice this morning.
- I've gotta get in there.
- Excuse me.
I was following up on a tip.
If you and the cavalry
had arrived any earlier,
you could have blown the thing.
As it is, the perp is dead, and
I'm on leave, all thanks to you.
Now, wait a minute.
You're the one who
pulled the trigger.
What do you mean,
you followed up on a tip?
Just what I said.
Somebody called Agent Farrell and
told her to check out the warehouse.
It was after hours. So she came
to my place and we discussed it.
I went to the warehouse. She helped
the police take your client into custody.
- You got a tip.
- We got a tip.
I got one for you, Mr. Matlock.
Stay off my tail
and out of my face.
Agent Farrell lives pretty
high on the hog. You know that.
Beach cottage in South
Carolina, Porsche in the garage.
What are you getting at?
I said it before.
I'll say it again.
The only way Kurt Becker could
have known to frame Ed Wingate
is if somebody in
the FBI told him to.
I hate to tell you
this, Mr. Matlock,
Agent Farrow was in my office briefing
me on the Sanborn kidnapping case
at the time that Dennis
Spiers was murdered.
So if Ed Wingate
really didn't kill him,
it had to have been Kurt Becker.
Unfortunately he's dead.
Hey.
It was a good plan.
It really was.
I knew there was a
chance I'd get caught.
Just didn't expect Kurt
Becker to get killed. Damn, oh...
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay, heh.
- Sorry I'm late.
- Are you all right?
Oh, I'm much better, thanks.
I had a nice chat
with Agent Pierce.
I hope you asked him how
he wound up in that warehouse
with Kurt Becker and
the ransom money.
Let me guess. An anonymous tip?
Yep.
I'm toast.
Well, maybe it's just as well.
I've obviously lost my edge, my ability
to outthink and outdo my opponents.
My professional
efficiency is defunct.
Oh, shut up.
We, the jury, find the defendants,
Barry Feldman and Tracey Riggins,
guilty of kidnapping.
Thank you, ladies and
gentlemen of the jury,
for a job well done.
You are excused from
further duty in this case
and free to leave
this courtroom.
Court is adjourned.
- Dad, Dad, Dad.
- I'm so sorry.
Hey, take it easy. It's all right. I
mean, we did it. We should pay.
- Yeah, but you're gonna go to prison.
- That's okay.
It'll give Tracey a chance
to lose some weight,
and I'll get to
visit my brother.
It's all my fault.
Billy, we kidnapped
you, remember?
Yeah, but you didn't
have anything against me.
You just wanted
to get back at Ben.
Yeah. Still do.
- Yeah. That cheapskate.
- What a jackass.
I knew I liked you guys.
What a pleasant surprise.
Come on in.
Why so quiet?
Sit down.
Matlock knows about this place.
Knows about the Porsche.
He's been asking
a lot of questions.
So? Heh.
As long as he can't prove
anything, who cares?
Thing is, the pressure
is getting to you.
You're getting
worried, depressed.
Heh, I am?
You're afraid everyone
is going to find out
you've been getting
rich kidnapping children.
You can't face the humiliation.
So,
you kill yourself.
Come on.
Freeze.
Give it up, Pierce.
I know you told me to stay off your
tail, but I just couldn't help myself.
We pulled off four kidnappings,
not only the Sanborn case.
Kurt Becker would make the
snatch and see to it nobody got hurt
while Alan and I would make
sure he made a clean getaway.
We'd meet up later
and split the ransom.
How much money did you make?
Each of us took in close to 400
thousand dollars in two years.
Dennis Spiers,
how did he fit in?
Kurt Becker saw him
snooping around his place.
Figured he was getting
too close for comfort.
He called me.
I called Alan Pierce.
Next thing I knew,
Dennis was dead.
Who killed him?
- It wasn't me. MAN:
Where were you that night?
Heh, as a matter of fact, I
was out in Glendale Hills,
casing the home of
a prospective victim.
You can't prove where
you were that night.
Uh, actually, I can.
A private security guard pulled
up next to us in his patrol car
and asked us what we were doing.
I flashed my shield
and told him to get lost.
I'm sure he'll remember.
You were with somebody.
Kurt Becker.
Well, it wasn't her, and
it wasn't Kurt Becker.
- It could have been Ed Wingate.
- Oh, come on.
This kidnapping ring
stuff's all very interesting,
but when it comes to the
murder of Dennis Spiers,
the facts still point
to Ed Wingate,
and since you seem to be going up
against a 20-year veteran of the FBI,
chances are they always will.
- Hmm.
- I'm sorry.
Dennis Spiers is supposed
to be a good agent.
Maybe he left us a clue.
Tape recorded
message would be nice.
Huh.
Well, let's see.
Now, he is, uh... He
was on the telephone.
Hello, uh-huh.
Yeah. Yeah. Conversation.
And then he hung it up.
And then he turned around
and there was the killer.
And he got shot, ooh.
But he didn't die right away.
He put up a big fight.
Fighting him, hitting him...
And he got hit again.
Then he fell down, unh. Dead.
And then the...
Oh, takes stuff out of his
pockets and some other stuff
to make it look like
it was a robbery.
- Oh, Dad, look at this.
- Heh, what?
Get up here and look at this.
Are you gonna give me a hand?
You know, you are too old
to be falling down like this.
I'm not too old to be
falling down like this.
Hurt myself.
Come here. Come here. Come here.
Look. Look at this.
- Now, look at this.
- Oh!
How long have you been
with the FBI, Agent Pierce?
- Going on 23 years.
- Uh-huh.
And, uh, what's
your current salary?
Sixty-five thousand dollars.
You married?
Yes, but, uh, my wife and I have
been separated for almost a year now.
You have an account in
a bank in the Bahamas,
don't you? PIERCE: Yes.
And only you have
access to that account?
Yes.
So all the money that's in it is
there because you put it there.
Yes.
Uh, here are some records from
that bank that we subpoenaed.
It's got all your
deposits and balances.
Would you just read
your current balance?
413,690 dollars.
Get out of town.
How can a man that makes
sixty-five thousand dollars a year
get his hands on
that kind of money?
I guess I just know how to save.
Heh, hmm.
You were recently arrested
and charged with kidnapping,
- weren't you?
- Yes.
And an agent under your
supervision named Brenda Farrell
was arrested and
charged for kidnapping, too.
- Yes.
- Only, she confessed.
She said that you and a man named
Kurt Becker and she were partners.
That doesn't make it true.
But you did kill Kurt
Becker, didn't you?
In the line of duty, yes.
And you were arrested for trying
to kill agent Farrell, weren't you?
Again, just because agent Farrell
says something does not mean it's true.
And when she told you that, uh,
Dennis Spiers was
closing in on Kurt Becker,
you killed him, too, so
that he would never know
that you and Kurt Becker and
agent Farrell were in cahoots.
No. I did not.
Hmm.
When, uh, was the last time you
were in, uh, Agent Spiers' house?
The night he died.
The police called me
when the body was found.
- So you were there the night he died.
- That's correct.
The reason I ask
is, uh, this a blow-up
uh, of one of the police
photos of the, uh, crime scene.
You see that stack of mail
there, with that plastic card on it,
with the magnetic,
uh, line there?
Yes, uh, that's Dennis' pass
key to the garage at headquarters.
Yeah.
Well, that's not quite true.
This is a blow-up
of that blow-up.
See. If you look carefully, you
can read the name on this pass card.
Could you read it aloud?
- Alan Pierce.
That's your pass key.
What's your pass key doing
at the scene of the crime?
I know what
happened. They, uh...
They issued that pass
key the day before,
only Dennis was so busy on the
Sanborn case he never got his.
So I swung by his
house to drop it off.
I must have given him the one
with my name on it by mistake.
Ah, that's what
happened all right.
Dennis Spiers, it's a simple mix up.
I just never noticed it until just now.
You're saying, this all occurred
the night before the murder.
That's right. I, uh, told my
secretary where I was going and why.
- You can ask her.
- Yeah. Well, okay.
Well, look at the date
on this postmark here.
- It says... Get your glasses.
- Hmm.
It says February 11th, see that?
He had just
brought this mail in.
He hadn't even gotten
around to opening it up.
Yet here's your pass key
right smack dab on top of it.
So what?
He probably used it
all day, like I used his,
got home after work,
took it out of his pocket,
dropped it on his desk,
where it landed on his mail.
You're right.
He did, he used his all day.
He was in and out of that office a lot
working on the Sanborn kidnapping.
I had, uh, Lieutenant Bronson
remove the pass key in question
from, uh, Mr. Spiers' house,
and he had the lab
ID the fingerprints on it.
Your fingerprints
are all over it.
You know how many of
Dennis Spiers' prints are on it?
None.
None. Now, how...?
How could he have
used this pass key all day
without leaving any
fingerprints on it?
You're right. He
couldn't. He couldn't.
The only way this card could have
wound up on top of this unopened mail
was there was
some kind of mix-up.
It fell out of your pocket
during the struggle, didn't it?
Landed on that mail.
And after it was over,
after you had killed him,
you picked up his card and left.
And when you found
out about the fight
that my client, Ed
Wingate, had had with him,
you told Kurt
Becker to frame him
by planting the murder
weapon at his house.
If you've got some other explanation,
I'm sure the jury would like to hear it.
That's what I thought.
Sure you don't
want a cup of coffee?
No, thanks. I'll grab
some at the office.
You're really looking forward
to getting back, aren't you?
Fighting crime is
my life, Leanne.
In fact, if either of you
ever has any trouble
that involves the smuggling of
drugs or illegal weapons, mail fraud,
bank robbery, racketeering,
anything like that,
rest assured, you
have a friend in the FBI.
That's very reassuring.
Ben, yoo-hoo.
In the kitchen, Billy.
I guess he's not
mad at you anymore.
Hmm, it didn't last.
Cliff, you remember Ed.
Billy Lewis, Ed
Wingate, FBI agent.
Never mind.
- Would you like some coffee?
- Mm, mm.
Ben, I owe you an apology.
In fact, I very well
may owe you my life.
I just want you to
know I'm grateful.
Really?
Come here.
- What?
- I want to give you a hug.
Guess who's been
seeing a therapist.
Yeah, he's been helping me deal
with the trauma of being kidnapped.
In fact, at first, I was gonna
make you pay his bills.
What?
But then I realized that that kind of
hostility doesn't get anybody anywhere.
It's time to become
friends, Ben.
It's time to make,
heh, real contact.
- Come here.
- No.
- It'll make us both feel better.
- Yes, it will. Come on.
- No.
- Yeah.
Dad.
- Come on.
- Let's go.
It's time.
- You're suffocating me.
- Good.
- Moron.
- Jackass.
www.tvsubtitles.net